We continue to offer funeral songs
to the ones selected out.
（涯）「俺たちは　淘汰される者に
葬送の歌を送り続ける」→
Hence "Funeral Parlor."
「故に　葬儀社」→
We will resist GHQ,
「俺たちは　あらがう」→
which rules this country
as though it owns the place.
「この国をわが物顔で支配する
ＧＨＱに」
（涯）「俺たちは戦う」
We will fight
「俺たちを淘汰しようとする
全てのものと」
against everything and everyone
that attempts to select us out.
"Self-Possession"
Now, I think you all know this,
（教師）えー。　もう　皆さん
ご存じかと思いますが→
but GHQ has declared
a Level 2 state of emergency
昨日の六本木の事件に関して→
in connection with
yesterday's incident in Roppongi.
ＧＨＱから　第２級の
非常事態宣言が出されました。→
If any of you have info on these terrorists
who call themselves "Funeral Parlor,"
葬儀社と名乗るテロリストについて
何か情報のある者は→
you're supposed to report it
to the authorities immediately.
速やかに　当局に
申し出るようにとのことです。→
Okay, one last thing.
それから　今日は　もう１つ。
このクラスに転入生があります。→
Our class has a new transfer student. Come on in!
入って。
≪（ドアの開く音）
A girl!
≪（生徒）うお　女子！
≪（生徒）へえ。　カワイイじゃん。
Hey, she's cute!
This is Inori Yuzuriha.
（教師）楪　いのり君だ。
≪（椅子を引く音）
（集）嘘…　でしょ？
This... can't be real...
What's up with you?
（生徒）何？　どしたの？
（生徒）あれ？　どっかで…。
Wait, I've seen her somewhere...
Inori?!
（生徒）いのり！？
（生徒）えっ　マジかよ！
For real?!
From Egoist?! That can't be right!
（生徒）ＥＧＯＩＳＴの？　まさか！？
（いのり）ホントだよ。
Of course it is.
（生徒たち）うおー！
≪（生徒たちの歓声）
Awesome!
So, everything that makes me whole
♪♪～
Ima kimi ni sasageyou
I'm yours
Nee, kono sekai ni wa takusan no
shiawase ga arun da ne
Itsuka futari nara
Dare ka ga kimi no koto
wo usotsuki to yonde
Kokoro nai kotoba de
kizu tsukeyou to shite mo
Sekai ga kimi no koto wo
shinjiyou to mo sezu ni
Ibara no kanmuri wo kabuseyou to shite mo
Watashi wa kimi dake no mikata ni nareru yo
Sono kodoku itami wo watashi wa shitte iru
So, everything that makes me whole
Ima kimi ni sasageyou
phanerosis
My name's Kanon Kusama. I'm the class rep.
（花音）私は　草間　花音。
クラス委員よ。　分からないこと…。
- Ask me if you have any questions, okay?
（集）《俺　葬儀社には
入らないって言ったのに→
- I said I wouldn't join Funeral Parlor,
- Ask me if you have any questions, okay?
- Do you have all your books and things already?
何で　学校なんかに来るんだ？》
- so why did she come to my school?
- If you're missing any,
I'll go borrow them from the teachers.
- We have P.E. today, so...
- I-Inori!
（颯太）い…　いのりさん！
（颯太）あの…。
葬儀社とかって　どう思います？
Um... So, what do you think about Funeral Parlor?
（花音）いきなり何よ！　颯太君！
Why would you just ask
that out of the blue, Souta?!
Well, Egoist's songs seem
kind of Funeral Parlor-ish, you know?
（颯太）だって　ＥＧＯＩＳＴの歌って
何か葬儀社っぽいじゃん！→
だから　好きかなーって。
（花音）なわけないでしょ！
So I thought maybe she liked them...
Yeah, right!
Oh, so, what are the other Egoist members like?
（生徒）ねえ！　じゃあ　ＥＧＯＩＳＴの
他のメンバーって　どんな人たち？
Hey, can I have your autograph?
（生徒）ねえ　サインしてくんない？（生徒）俺も　俺も！
Me too, me too!
（谷尋）いいかげんにしろよ。→
Cut it out, guys.
楪さん　困ってるじゃん。
You're putting Yuzuriha on the spot.
（谷尋）ごめんな。
こいつ　魂館　颯太ってんだけど→
Sorry. This guy's name is
Souta Tamadate, and he's a huge fan of yours.
すげえ　君のファンでさ。
無礼は許してやってよ。
So forgive him his rudeness, okay?
あっ　ちなみに　俺は　寒川　谷尋。
Oh, and I'm Yahiro Samukawa, by the way.
あぁ…　俺と谷尋と
あそこの　集ってやつで→
Me and Yahiro and Shu over there
現代映像文化研究会って
同好会をつくってて…。
formed this club called
the "Contemporary Visual Culture Club,"
それで　あの…！
and I was wondering... um!
だーから　焦るなって。
みんなもだ。
I'm telling you, man, chill out.
You guys, too.
俺たち　これから　ずっと
一緒のクラスなんだからさ。→
We're going to be in the same
class for the rest of the year.
慌てないでいこうぜ。　なっ？
So let's just take it slow, okay?
≪（生徒）ごめんね　いのりさん。
≪（生徒）ごめん　悪かったね。
Sorry, Inori.
Sorry, my bad.
（集）《でも　あの子が
この学校に来たの→
I just know that her coming here
must have something to do with me, though...
どう考えても
俺と無関係じゃないよな…》
One, two, three, four.
（花音）１・２・３・４…。
（生徒）でもさ　実際　見てると→
Man, when you see Inori in person,
she's kinda like a doll, huh?
いのりって　何か人形っぽくね？
（集）えっ？　あっ　そうだね。
Hmm? Yeah, I guess so.
リアルの方が
ＣＧっぽいっていうか…。
Like she looks more like
CG in real life, or something...
How could you say that, Shu?!
（颯太）何　言ってんだよ　集！
いのりはＣＧなんかじゃねえよ！
目を覚ませよ　バカ！→
Inori is not CG! Open your eyes, moron!
お前　そういうこと
ぜってえ　本人に言うなよ！→
Don't you ever say that to her face, got it?
傷つきやすいんだからな
いのりは！
Inori's sensitive and easily hurt, you know!
《「バカ」って言われた…》
He called me a moron...
《俺の傷つきやすさの方は
見過ごされてもいいのか？》
Is it okay for people to ignore
how easily hurt I might be?
《…って　また
自分のことばっかりか　俺は》
There I go thinking only
about myself again, huh...
《とにかく　もう　彼女とは
関わらないようにしよう！》
Anyway, I'll just try not to
get involved with her anymore!
《うん！》
（電子音）
わあっ！
い…　いのりさん！　何で？
I-Inori?!
Why?
何　この荷物！？
What are all these boxes?
ま…　待ってよ。
W-Wait!
いのりさん！　うっ…！
Inori!
What the heck was that for?!
ちょっと　何すんのー！？
あっ　ねえ！
Hey! Wait!
待ってよ！
うわっ！
うっ！
Wait... stop it...
ちょ…！　やめ…。
うぅ！
どうして　うちに来るの？
ってか　何で　鍵　開けられんの？
Why are you at my apartment?!
More like, why can you open the door?!
ふゅーねるが　やってくれた。
Funell did it for me.
…って。
Uh...
えっと…　いのりさん？
Excuse me, Inori?
いのり。
Don't be polite.
Uh, I really can't be rude right off the bat...
いや　いきなり呼び捨てとか
無理だから…。
ねえ　集。
Hey, Shu.
な…　何？
Wh-What?
I'm starving.
おなか減った。
へっ？
痛っ。
Ow.
じゃあ　何がいい？
So... what are you hungry for?
おにぎり。
Rice balls.
（ヤン）「六本木の件→
Well, Keido, how will you take
responsibility for what happened in Roppongi?
どう責任を取ってくれるのだね？
茎道君」
（茎道）ご安心を。→
Rest easy, Sir.
以後　葬儀社に関する件は
嘘界少佐の担当としますので。
I will be putting Major Segai in charge
of all Funeral Parlor-related matters going forward.
Segai?!
（高官）「嘘界を！？」
（高官）「何者かね？」
Who is he?
Are you familiar with "Norma Gene"?
（茎道）ノーマジーンを
ご存じですか？
It's a genetic drug that's been in vogue lately.
（ヤン）「最近　流行している
ジーンドラッグだ」
Am I right, Dr. Ouma?
「違ったかな？　ドクター桜満」
（春夏）はい。→
Yes, Sir. It was an incidental discovery
アポカリプスウイルスのワクチン開発時に
偶然　発見されたものです。
during the development of
the Apocalypse Virus vaccine.
When I assigned him to
figure out its distribution channels,
（茎道）その密売ルートを
追わせていましたが　嘘界少佐は→
he gave me the whole picture
of the industry within a week.
１週間で
全容を解明してしまいました。
Then he's sharp?
（高官）「切れ者か」
（茎道）過ぎるほどです。→
Almost too sharp.
彼は　ふさわしい獲物を与えれば
全力で狩り→
If we give him worthy prey,
he'll hunt it with all his energy...
そして　つるす。
...and hang it up to dress.
My apologies; that was a work email.
（嘘界）失礼。
仕事のメールでした。
Now, how far had we gotten?
で　どこまで
進んだんでしたっけ？→
Ah, yes. "To talk, or not to be,
that is the question," I believe?
ああ　「しゃべるべきか　死すべきかそれが問題だ」辺りでしたっけ。→
巻いていきましょう。
Let's hoist him up.
Man, this is a problem...
それにしても困ったな。
母さん帰ってきたら
何て説明すれば…。
How do I explain it to Mom when she gets home?
Haruka Ouma.
Senior Researcher at Sephirah Genomics.
桜満　春夏。
セフィラゲノミクス主任研究員。
帰宅は　週に一度程度。
あと数日は　戻る見込みがない。
Only comes home about once a week.
Unlikely to be back here for several days.
全部　調査済みってわけか。
So, you've done a whole background check.
A burden?
迷惑？
えっ？
桜満　集は　いのりが迷惑？
Shu Ouma, am I a burden to you?
Um... you're not a burden, but...
えっと　迷惑じゃないけど→
何で　君が来たのか
分かんなくて…。
I just don't know why you're here...
あなたを守るため。
えっ？
To protect you.
≪（チャイム）
C-Coming!
はーい！
よっ！　遅くに悪いな。
Yo, sorry to come so late.
どうしたの？
（谷尋）ちょっと思い出してさ。→
What's up?
I just remembered something.
これ　この前　話してた映画。
見るか？
This is that movie we were
talking about. Wanna watch it?
Um, thanks... You came all the way here for that?
あ…　ありがと…。
でも　このために　わざわざ？
今日のお前　様子　おかしかった。
…ような気がした。
You were acting weird today.
Or at least, I got that feeling.
昨日　何かあった？
Did something happen yesterday?
何かあったかな？　分かんない。
Good question... I'm not really sure.
そっか。
≪（足音）
I see.
あれ？　君　どうして…。
Huh?
Why are you?
連絡が来た。
一緒に来て　集。
I got a communication. Come with me, Shu.
あぁ…。
色々　事情があるんだよ。
（谷尋）どういう事情？
Er, there are some circumstances behind this!
What circumstances?
分かんない。
I'm not sure.
Anyway, see you tomorrow!
取りあえず　あした！
何かあったら　言えよ！
≪ありがとう。　そうする！
Tell me if anything happens, all right?
Thanks, I will!
寒川　谷尋は　集の友達？
Is Yahiro Samukawa your friend?
なんじゃないかな…　たぶん。
Probably, I guess.
あいつは偉いんだ。
He's a great person.
He really looks at the people
around him, and he can be sympathetic...
自分以外の人のことを
ちゃんと見て　思いやれて→
Totally different from me.
僕とは大違いだ。
Don't you have any friends, Inori?
いのりさんは　いないの？　友達。
Does a person have to have friends?
友達って
いなければ　いけないもの？
Yeah, I just finished. The OAU is very interested.
ああ　今　終わった。
ＯＡＵは乗り気だ。
They gave me a condition, though.
I'll report in more detail later.
ただ　１つ条件を出された。
後で詳しく報告する。
ご苦労だったな。
あ…　いや。
Thanks for coming.
Eh...
すごい格好だね。
That's some outfit.
とても　指名手配犯には
見えないよ。
You don't look like a wanted criminal at all.
銃を持って走り回るだけでは
世の中は変わらないからな。
You can't change the world
just by running around with guns.
鶫。　尾行は？
Tsugumi, anyone tailing them?
（鶫）オールクリアでーす。
All clear!
More importantly, what did you mean
by sending Inori to my school and apartment?
それより　何のつもり？
いのりさんを
学校や　僕のうちに…。
問題が発生した。
We have a problem.
昨日の作戦中
俺たちを目撃していたやつがいる。
Someone witnessed us during the battle yesterday.
フォートの住人ならば
対処できたが→
If they were from the fort
I could have taken care of it,
but it seems they're an outsider.
どうやら　外の人間。
A student from your school.
お前と同じ学校に通う
学生だったようだ。
From my school? Why would?
うちの学生が！？　どうして…。
ノーマジーン。
聞いたことはあるか？
"Norma Gene." Have you heard of it?
確か　最近　はやってる
ドラッグで…。
Yeah, I think it's the popular drug these days...
それを買いに来てた？
They were here to buy it?
During the deal, they called themselves "Sugar."
取引のときは
シュガーを名乗っていたらしい。
むろん　偽名だろうが。
Though that's probably an alias, of course.
There's a good chance they saw you and Inori.
お前と　いのりは　高確率で
そいつに目撃されている。
Find them.
捜し出せ。
そんな！
Are you kidding? How many
students do you think go to my school?!
うちの学校に
何人　生徒がいると思ってるのさ！
見つけようがないって！
There's no way to find them!
いや　ある。
ヴォイドを取り出せ。
Actually, there is.
Draw out their Void.
あっ。　そうか。
見える…。
I get it, you can see them.
You can tell what people's
Voids are, can't you, Gai?
分かるんだね？
涯には　ヴォイドが。
ほう？
だって　六本木のとき→
Oho.
I mean, you couldn't have made
that plan in Roppongi if you hadn't known.
分かってなきゃ
あの作戦は立てられない。
理解が早くて助かる。
確かに　俺にはヴォイドが分かる。
It's convenient how quickly you figure things out.
It's true: I can tell people's Voids.
And in that battle,
I sensed the presence of the witness,
そして　あのとき
俺は　目撃者がいるのを感じ→
and I saw their Void.
そいつのヴォイドを見た。
現行の災害臨時法制下では
テロリストに人権はない。
Under the Temporary
Disaster Law currently in effect,
terrorists have no human rights.
目撃者に特定されれば
お前も無傷では　いられない。
If the witness identifies you,
you won't escape harm.
分かっているな？
I trust you understand?
I've informed Inori of the Void's shape.
ヴォイドの形状は
いのりに教えてある。
If you value your peaceful
everyday life, protect it for yourself.
平穏な日常が大事なら
自分で守れ。
集？
Shu?
大丈夫だよ　やれるから。
It's okay. I can do it.
ヴォイドのルール　覚えた？
Have you memorized the Void rules?
"Voids can only be drawn from
people seventeen years old or younger."
一つ。　ヴォイドは
１７歳以下の人間からしか出せない。
理由は不明。
The reason is unclear.
Or else it's a secret from me.
もしくは　僕には内緒。
うん。
一つ。　取り出された相手は→
"When you withdraw a Void from someone,
that person loses their memories
of the time surrounding the event."
ヴォイドが取り出される前後の
記憶を喪失する。
That's from the shock of the intron
memory field being released, I think?
これは　イントロンの記憶野が
解放されたときのショック。
…だったっけ？
うん。
《でも　それなら好都合》
But that works in my favor.
《とにかく　今は実験だ》
Anyway, right now I need to experiment.
Hare will forgive me even if I screw up...
《祭なら　万一　失敗しても
許してくれる》
《…ような気がする》
...I think.
《今だ！》
Now!
あっ！　あぁ…。
あぁ…！
なぜだ…。
なぜ　こんなことに…。
Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
Wow.
（生徒）すっげ！
（生徒）勇気あんな。
He's got guts!
（祭）どうして？　集。
言ってくれれば　私は　いつでも…。
Why, Shu? If you'd just
said something, I would have!
（花音）キャー！！
うっ…　うわっ！
集。
Shu.
待ちなさい　桜満　集！！
Hold it right there, Shu Ouma!
（電子音）
"Scum!!!!"
終わりだ…。
"He needs to get that sex drive under control"
"What a total creep"
It's over.
And I was on track to get through
three years of school without standing out!
目立たずに　３年間を
泳ぎ切るはずだったのに！
みんな　今の忘れてくれないかな。
もしくは死んでくんないかな…。
Maybe everyone could do me
a favor and forget about this?
Or die?
How did I screw it up?
何で失敗したんだろ？
Her eyes, maybe.
目かも。
目？
Eyes?
You weren't looking at them.
さっき　集は見てなかった。
でも　ヴォイドを出すのには必要。
But that's necessary when
you're drawing out a Void.
そんなルールあるの？
That's another rule?
いや　それ　無理だよ。
But I can't do that!
I get nervous when I make
eye contact with people,
僕　人と目が合ってると緊張して
話が　すっぽ抜けちゃうんだよね。
and I lose my grip on the conversation...
集。
Shu.
はい…。
Yes?
私が目を見てると思う？
Do you think I'm looking into your eyes?
私は　集の眉と眉の間を見てる。
I'm looking between your eyebrows.
相手が見られたと思うことが
重要だって　涯が言ってた。
Gai told me the important thing is
for them to think you made eye contact.
《今度こそ仕留める！》
I'm gonna bring someone down this time!
♪♪（鼻歌）
颯太！
Souta!
はあ？　あっ！
うぉぉぉぉぉ！！
どうした！？　集！
What's wrong, Shu?!
全部　忘れろー！！
Forget everything!
ぷはぁ！！
（颯太）うぐぁぁ！
うわあぁぁぁ！！
これ？
違う。
Is this it?
No.
まあ　そうだよね。
分かってたけどさ。
Yeah... I pretty much knew it wasn't...
《でも　コツは　つかんだ！》
But I've got the hang of it now!
Just you watch: now this starts for real.
《見てろ。
ここからが本番だ！》
いっくぞー！
Here I go!
Pardon me!
すいませーん！
違う。
No.
Pardon me!
すいませーん！
違う。
No.
すいませーん！
Pardon me!
ホント　すいませーん！
Sorry, pardon me!
マジで　ホント　す…。
Seriously, I'm sor...
Huh?
あれ？　こ…　これは…。
What is this?!
あっ！　うっ…。
うぅぅ…。
でさ→
Okay, so what Void am I
actually supposed to get, exactly?
結局　僕は　どんなヴォイドを
取り出せばいいの？
はさみ。
そんなんなの？
Shears.
Really?
Mm-hmm. You'll know them when you see them.
うん。　見れば分かる。
ヴォイドって何なの？
どうして　いろんな形があるの？
What are Voids?
Why do they come in so many forms?
ヴォイドの形や機能は→
A Void's form and function
reflect things like the person's fears or complexes.
持ち主の恐怖や
コンプレックスを反映している。
いわば　心の形。
You could say it's the shape of their heart.
Voids are... the shape of their hearts?
心の形…。　ヴォイドが…。
Huh?
あれ？　じゃあ　何で　君からは→
Then... why is yours...
剣が出てくるの？
...a sword?
≪（足音）
There you are!
（花音）いた！　桜満　集！
トォォォ！
Shu Ouma!
Crap!
ヤバっ！
（谷尋）集！　こっちだ！
Shu!
This way!
≪（花音）待ちなさい！
Hold it right there!
ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…。
（谷尋）ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…。
ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…。
This is rough! I've done nothing
but run around since yesterday.
きっついなぁ…。
昨日から　逃げ回ってばっかりだ。
葬儀社に入ってたら
そんなもんじゃ済まないだろ。
Yeah, but if you'd joined Funeral Parlor,
they'd have made you do worse.
True.
だね。　ハハハ…。
委員長も　もう　しばらくすれば
頭が冷えるだろうからさ→
The class rep will probably
cool down after a while,
そしたら　謝りに行こうぜ。
so let's go apologize to her then.
そうだね。
でも　許してくれるかな？
Yeah... But will she forgive me, I wonder?
はさみで　体を
ちょん切られちゃうんじゃない？
She might just cut me into pieces with shears.
What, are you talking
about that movie from last night?
（谷尋）何？　昨日の映画の話？
うん。
前から思ってたけど→
Your tastes are kind of surprising,
you know? I've thought so for a while.
谷尋の趣味って
ちょっと意外だよね。
Where did that come from?
（谷尋）何だよ　いきなり…。
責めてるわけじゃないんだけど。
I'm not criticizing you;
I'm just trying to say appearances
can be pretty deceiving sometimes...
人の中身と見た目は
結構　違うよねって言いたいんだ。
...Sugar.
シュガー。
♪♪～
あっ！
So I was seen.
（谷尋）やっぱり
見られてたんだな。　軽蔑したか？
And now you scorn me?
いや…。
何か事情があるんでしょ？
No... I mean, knowing you,
there must have been circumstances, right?
谷尋のことだもん　何か理由が…。
（谷尋）うるせえよ！！
Some kind of reason...
Shut up!
まだ続けるのか　友達ごっこを！
You're gonna keep on playing at being friends?!
It was all over from
the moment you called me "Sugar"!
今　お前が　俺を　シュガーと呼んだ時点で　全部終わりだろうが！
悩んでるふりして　善人ぶるな！
So don't get all sanctimonious and
pretend like you're conflicted about it!
（谷尋）お前みたいなのが
俺を無害と決め付けるから→
It's because guys like you
just assume I'm harmless
俺は　そういうやつで
居続けなくちゃならん！→
that I have to keep acting that way!
俺でない誰かを
演じ続けなくちゃならん！→
I have to keep pretending to be someone I'm not!
It's all your fault!
全部　お前のせいだ！！
谷尋！
Yahiro!
（谷尋）うっ！　ぐぁぁぁ！
This is Yahiro's?
これが　谷尋の…！？
決まりね。
駄目だ！！
That's that, then.
No!
駄目だ　そんなの…。
You can't do that.
どうして？
彼は　誘惑に負けた人。
Why not?
Gai says he succumbed to temptation,
クリアしておかないと
脅威になるって　涯が。
and he'll be a threat to us
if we don't clear him up now.
君たちに　何が分かんの！！
What do you guys know?!
集…。
Shu...
変かもしれないけど→
Maybe it's weird,
僕は　彼が頑張ってつくった
表面の谷尋を忘れたくない！
but I don't want to forget the surface
Yahiro he worked so hard to build!
全部　嘘だったって
決め付けたくない！
I don't want to just assume it was all a lie!
だから　それを下ろして！
So put that down, Inori!
いのり！！
あっ…。
集が　そう言うなら。
If you say so, Shu.
Thank you.
ありがとう。
《その後　目を覚ました谷尋と
僕は　約束を交わした》
Afterward, when Yahiro woke up,
we made a promise to each other.
《彼は　葬儀社のことを
僕は　ノーマジーンのことを→
We promised he wouldn't tell
anyone about Funeral Parlor,
決して　人には話さない
という約束だ》
and I wouldn't tell anyone about Norma Gene.
《僕は　初めて　本当に
谷尋と知り合った気がした…》
I felt like it was the first time
Yahiro and I really met.
Report from Inoreen!
"Witness problem solved. Steer clear from now on."
[無線]（鶫）いのりんから報告。→
「目撃者の件は解決。
今後は　手出し無用」だって。
Oho.
ほう？
[無線]（鶫）いいの？
Is that okay?
好きにさせるさ。
I'll let them do what they want.
集。　ずっと　そばにいても　いい？
えっ？
Shu... can I stay with you forever?
知りたいの。
集のこと。　みんなのこと。
I want to know you. And the others. So...
だから…。
す…　好きにすればいいと思うよ。
I-I think you can do what you want.
≪（ブレーキ音）
うわっ！　何だ？
What is this?
Hey, who are they?
≪おい！　何だ？　あれ。
≪ＧＨＱ！？
GHQ?!
あっ。
悪いな。
Sorry.
えっ？　何？
What?
どういうこと？　谷尋！
What gives, Yahiro?
What gives?!
どういうこと！？
（嘘界）桜満　集君。
えっ？
Shu Ouma.
あなたを逮捕します。
You...
...are under arrest.
♪♪～
Mou anata kara ai sareru koto mo
Hitsuyou to sareru koto mo nai
Soshite watashi wa kou shite hitori bocchi de
Ano toki anata wa nante itta no?
Todokanai kotoba wa chuu wo mau
Wakatteru no ni kyou mo shite shimau
Kanawanu negaigoto wo
Hanasanaide gyutto te wo nigitte ite
Anata to futari tsuzuku to itte
Tsunaida sono te wa atatakakute yasashikatta